

Hana Le

Entry Level Statistician | Data Scientist

My Contact

Marsfield, NSW 2122



in linkedin.com/in/hangIth



hana-le.com



PR in progress

Education Background

Master of Applied Statistics

Macquarie University Completed in Dec 2022 **WAM 85**

Master of Project Management

University of Queensland

Bachelor of Science

Vietnam National University, Hanoi

Technical Skills

- R
- SOL
- Tableau
- **Excel Data Analysis**
- Python
- Data Visualisation
- Statistical Modeling
- Data Analysis

Soft Skills

- · Skilled in stakeholder partnership management across sectors
- Adaptable to diverse working styles
- Experienced in diverse team collaboration
- Solution-focused and data-driven

About Me

A recent Applied Statistics graduate with a WAM of 85 and a passion for utilising computational techniques to analyse and interpret data. Proficient in R, SQL, Tableau, and Excel with in-depth knowledge of contemporary statistical methods. Seeking opportunities to further develop skills and bring 6+ years of project management experience in UN and NGO settings, including data collection and analysis, to the table.

Professional Experience

Data Entry Officer | Avant Mutual

Key responsibilities:

Reviewing, verifying and compiling data in the database system.

Program Officer | Oxfam Organisation

2018 - 2019

Key responsibilities:

Design and implementation management of a series of gender and development projects, delivered in partnership with both nongovernment organisations and government agencies.

Project Coordinator | International Labour Organisation

2015 - 2017

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USD1.5m portfolio of projects aimed at improving labour practices in private sector enterprises in Viet Nam.

Project Manager | Care International Organisation

2010 - 2014

Key responsibilities:

Implementation management of a USDIm portfolio of projects aimed at delivering public health interventions for disadvantaged and vulnerable communities.

Achievements

- · Successfully managed all projects in charge, including delivering on time, within budget, and to the agreed quality specifications.
- Achieved a full scholarship for the master's program at Queensland University.